<graphml xmlns="http://graphml.graphdrawing.org/xmlns" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://graphml.graphdrawing.org/xmlns http://graphml.graphdrawing.org/xmlns/1.0/graphml.xsd">
  <key id="d6" for="edge" attr.name="source_id" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d5" for="edge" attr.name="description" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d4" for="edge" attr.name="weight" attr.type="double" />
  <key id="d3" for="node" attr.name="entity_type" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d2" for="node" attr.name="source_id" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d1" for="node" attr.name="description" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d0" for="node" attr.name="type" attr.type="string" />
  <graph edgedefault="undirected">
    <node id="PROJECT GUTENBERG">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">Project Gutenberg is an online platform that offers free eBooks, including "A Christmas Carol"
Project Gutenberg is an organization that distributes electronic works, including 'A Christmas Carol', without copyright restrictions in the United States
Project Gutenberg is a collection of electronic works, most of which are in the public domain in the United States
Project Gutenberg is a digital library offering free access to a large collection of electronic works
Project Gutenberg is an initiative focused on the free distribution of electronic works in formats readable by a wide variety of computers. It relies on volunteers and donations to maintain its collection and mission.</data>
      <data key="d2">0ddc17ea5e566006c000b4013f2181a5,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa,cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHARLES DICKENS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Charles Dickens is the author of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ARTHUR RACKHAM">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Arthur Rackham is the illustrator of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="J. B. LIPPINCOTT COMPANY">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">J. B. Lippincott Company is the original publisher of "A Christmas Carol" in Philadelphia and New York</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="UNITED STATES">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The country where Project Gutenberg is based and where the eBook is freely available
Mentioned in the context of a security that would become irrelevant if there were no days to count by
The country where Project Gutenberg operates and distributes electronic works without copyright restrictions
The country where most of the Project Gutenberg works are in the public domain and where the copyright laws mentioned apply
The United States is the country where the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation operates and complies with charity laws.</data>
      <data key="d2">2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6,aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa,cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="A CHRISTMAS CAROL">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A Christmas Carol is a novella by Charles Dickens, first published in 1843, that tells the story of Ebenezer Scrooge's transformation after being visited by ghosts
</data>
      <data key="d2">2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SUZANNE SHELL">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Suzanne Shell is one of the producers of the Project Gutenberg eBook of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="JANET BLENKINSHIP">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Janet Blenkinship is one of the producers of the Project Gutenberg eBook of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ONLINE DISTRIBUTED PROOFREADING TEAM">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Online Distributed Proofreading Team is a group that helped produce the Project Gutenberg eBook of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PHILADELPHIA">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Philadelphia is one of the cities where "A Christmas Carol" was originally published</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="NEW YORK">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">New York is one of the cities where "A Christmas Carol" was originally published</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BOB CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Bob Cratchit is a character in "A Christmas Carol," the clerk to Ebenezer Scrooge
Bob Cratchit is Scrooge's clerk who asks for a day off on Christmas Eve and enjoys sliding on Cornhill
Bob Cratchit is Scrooge's clerk who lives in a modest four-roomed house and earns fifteen 'Bob' a week
Bob Cratchit is a character who works hard to support his family, earning only fifteen 'Bob' a week. He is the father of the Cratchit family and is described as wearing threadbare clothes and a long comforter. He is also very caring towards his son, Tiny Tim.
Bob Cratchit is a member of the Cratchit family who took Tiny Tim beside him at the table and proposed a toast
Bob Cratchit is an employee of Scrooge and the father of Tiny Tim
Bob Cratchit is a poor man who is the father of Tiny Tim and husband to Mrs. Cratchit
Bob Cratchit is an employee of Scrooge, to whom Scrooge plans to send a large turkey as a surprise gift
Bob Cratchit is Scrooge's employee who is late to work but receives a raise and assistance from Scrooge
Bob Cratchit is an employee of Scrooge who is promised a raise and assistance for his struggling family</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="EBENEZER SCROOGE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Ebenezer Scrooge is the main character in "A Christmas Carol," known for being a grasping, covetous old man
Ebenezer Scrooge is a character who is confronted by a ghost and is deeply troubled by the encounter

Ebenezer Scrooge is the main character who wakes up in a dark room and experiences strange events
Ebenezer Scrooge is the name on the neglected grave that Scrooge reads</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PETER CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Peter Cratchit is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a son of Bob Cratchit
Peter Cratchit is one of Bob Cratchit's children who is considering a job opportunity</data>
      <data key="d2">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TIM CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Tim Cratchit, also known as Tiny Tim, is a character in "A Christmas Carol," the youngest son of Bob Cratchit and a cripple</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MR. FEZZIWIG">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Mr. Fezziwig is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a kind-hearted, jovial old merchant
</data>
      <data key="d2">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FRED">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Fred is a character in "A Christmas Carol," the nephew of Ebenezer Scrooge
Fred is Scrooge's nephew who invited Scrooge to dinner

Fred is Scrooge's nephew who hosted the game and led the toast to Scrooge
Fred is Scrooge's nephew who welcomes him warmly to dinner</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PAST">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Ghost of Christmas Past is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a phantom showing things past
The Ghost of Christmas Past is a spirit that visits Scrooge to show him scenes from his past
The Ghost of Christmas Past is a supernatural entity that illuminates Scrooge's memories and interactions
The Ghost of Christmas Past is a supernatural entity that shows Scrooge scenes from his past
The Spirit that shows Scrooge scenes from his past
The Ghost of Christmas Past is one of the spirits that visits Scrooge to show him scenes from his past</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Ghost of Christmas Present is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a spirit of a kind, generous, and hearty nature
The Ghost of Christmas Present is a jolly giant who appears to Scrooge, dressed in a green robe bordered with white fur, and surrounded by festive decorations and food
The Ghost of Christmas Present is a specific manifestation of the Spirit that appears to Scrooge
The Ghost of Christmas Present is the spirit who accompanies Scrooge and blesses Bob Cratchit's house
The Ghost of Christmas Present is a spirit who blesses Bob Cratchit's house with the sprinklings of his torch. He is a supernatural entity who spreads joy and blessings.
The Ghost of Christmas Present is a supernatural entity that shows Scrooge scenes from the present

The Ghost of Christmas Present is one of the spirits that visits Scrooge to show him the current state of his life and the lives of others
The Ghost of Christmas Present is a spirit that showed Scrooge the joy and festivities of Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS YET TO COME">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come is a character in "A Christmas Carol," an apparition showing the shadows of things which yet may happen
The solemn Phantom that shows Scrooge the future
The Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come is a spirit that shows Scrooge visions of the future
The Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come is one of the spirits that visits Scrooge to show him the potential future consequences of his actions</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GHOST OF JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Ghost of Jacob Marley is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a spectre of Scrooge's former partner in business
The Ghost of Jacob Marley is the spectral form of Scrooge's former business partner who warns him of the visits by the three spirits</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="JOE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Joe is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a marine-store dealer and receiver of stolen goods
Joe is a character who discussed bed-curtains with a woman
Joe is an old man who appraises and buys items from others</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MR. TOPPER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Mr. Topper is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a bachelor</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DICK WILKINS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Dick Wilkins is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a fellow apprentice of Scrooge's
Dick Wilkins is a fellow apprentice of Ebenezer, who was very much attached to him</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BELLE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Belle is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a comely matron and an old sweetheart of Scrooge's
Belle is the wife of the master of the house and an old acquaintance of Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CAROLINE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Caroline is a character in "A Christmas Carol," the wife of one of Scrooge's debtors
Caroline is a woman who feels a mix of hope and relief upon hearing about the death of a merciless creditor
Caroline is a character who feels relief at the death of a merciless creditor</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MRS. CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Mrs. Cratchit is a character in "A Christmas Carol," the wife of Bob Cratchit
Mrs. Cratchit is Bob Cratchit's wife, who is described as being dressed out but poorly
Mrs. Cratchit is Bob Cratchit's wife. She is described as being dressed poorly in a twice-turned gown but makes a good show with ribbons. She is responsible for laying the cloth and preparing the meal.
Mrs. Cratchit is a member of the Cratchit family who made the gravy and prepared the pudding for the family dinner
Mrs. Cratchit is Bob Cratchit's wife who expresses strong negative feelings towards Scrooge
Mrs. Cratchit is the wife of Bob Cratchit and mother of Tiny Tim
Mrs. Cratchit is Bob's wife who speaks about Peter and Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BELINDA CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Belinda Cratchit is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a daughter of Bob Cratchit
Belinda Cratchit is the second daughter of Bob and Mrs. Cratchit. She assists her mother in preparing the meal and is described as being brave in ribbons.</data>
      <data key="d2">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MARTHA CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Martha Cratchit is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a daughter of Bob Cratchit
Martha Cratchit is the eldest daughter of Bob and Mrs. Cratchit. She arrives late due to work and is warmly welcomed by her family. She hides to surprise her father, Bob.
Martha Cratchit is a poor apprentice at a milliner's and one of Bob Cratchit's children</data>
      <data key="d2">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MRS. DILBER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Mrs. Dilber is a character in "A Christmas Carol," a laundress
Mrs. Dilber is a woman who enters Old Joe's shop with a heavy bundle
Mrs. Dilber is a woman who brings items to Joe for appraisal and sale</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792,bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Fan is a character in "A Christmas Carol," the sister of Scrooge
Fan is Scrooge's younger sister who comes to bring him home for Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MRS. FEZZIWIG">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Mrs. Fezziwig is a character in "A Christmas Carol," the worthy partner of Mr. Fezziwig
Mrs. Fezziwig is a character who danced with Old Fezziwig
Mrs. Fezziwig is the wife of Old Fezziwig, known for her substantial smile and participation in the Christmas Eve festivities
Mrs. Fezziwig is the partner of Mr. Fezziwig, equally lively and skilled in dancing, and participates in the domestic ballMrs. Fezziwig is the partner of Old Fezziwig, equally lively and skilled in dancing, and participates in the domestic ball</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="THE FIRST OF THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The First of the Three Spirits is the second chapter of "A Christmas Carol," where Scrooge is visited by the Ghost of Christmas Past
The First of the Three Spirits is the initial supernatural entity that will visit Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d2">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="THE SECOND OF THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Second of the Three Spirits is the third chapter of "A Christmas Carol," where Scrooge is visited by the Ghost of Christmas Present</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="THE LAST OF THE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Last of the Spirits is the fourth chapter of "A Christmas Carol," where Scrooge is visited by the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="THE END OF IT">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The End of It is the fifth and final chapter of "A Christmas Carol," where Scrooge's transformation is complete</data>
      <data key="d2">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MARLEY'S GHOST">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1">
Marley's Ghost is an event where Marley's ghost appears
The apparition of Marley that appears to Scrooge, causing him great fear and disbelief
Marley's Ghost is the apparition of Jacob Marley, who warns Scrooge about his fate and the visits of three spirits
Marley's Ghost is a supernatural entity that haunts Scrooge and warns him of future visitations</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FEZZIWIG">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Old Fezziwig is a character who stood out to dance with Mrs. Fezziwig
Fezziwig is an old gentleman who was Scrooge's employer during his apprenticeship
Old Fezziwig is a jovial and benevolent gentleman who runs a business and is known for his lively and generous spirit, especially during Christmas Eve celebrations
Old Fezziwig is a character who is described as a lively and skilled dancer, hosting a domestic ball and spreading cheer among his guests</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Scrooge is a character known for being tight-fisted, squeezing, wrenching, grasping, scraping, clutching, and covetous. He was Marley's business partner and sole executor
Scrooge is a miserly, solitary old man who is described as cold and unfeeling, both physically and emotionally. He is known for his disdain for Christmas and human sympathy.
Scrooge is a character who is cynical about Christmas and is the uncle of the nephew in the text
Scrooge is a character who is known for his miserly and uncharitable nature, particularly during the Christmas season
Scrooge is a character who is depicted as a miserly and grumpy individual, known for his disdain towards Christmas and his clerk
Scrooge is the main character who is experiencing strange events in his house
Scrooge is a character who is skeptical and disbelieving of supernatural occurrences, particularly the ghost of Marley
Scrooge is a character who is being visited by ghosts and is warned about his fate
Scrooge is the main character who is being visited by the Ghost of Christmas Past
Scrooge is a character who is reflecting on his past and experiencing a range of emotions, from joy to sorrow, as he revisits memories of Christmas
Scrooge is a character who is reflecting on his past experiences, including interactions with his sister and his schoolmaster
Scrooge is a character who reflects on his past, showing a range of emotions from joy to agitation, and interacts with the Ghost
Scrooge is a character who is reflecting on his past and is being shown scenes by a ghost
Scrooge is a central character who experiences various supernatural events and reflections on his life
Scrooge is the main character who is experiencing strange and supernatural events in his room
Scrooge is a character who interacts with the Spirit and learns lessons from it
Scrooge is a character who interacts with the Spirit and questions him about his actions and intentions
Scrooge is a character who shows concern for Tiny Tim's future and speaks with the Ghost
Scrooge is a wealthy, stingy, and unfeeling man who is the subject of much discussion and disdain among the Cratchit family
Scrooge is a character who is being guided by a Ghost through various scenes of Christmas celebrations
Scrooge is a central character who is surprised by the laughter of his nephew and is described as a comical old fellow who is not very pleasant but very rich
Scrooge is a character who is known for his dislike of Christmas and his solitary nature
Scrooge is a central character who participated in the games and was the subject of the guessing game
The main character who is being shown visions by the Spirit
Scrooge is the main character who is being guided by the Phantom
Scrooge is a character who is observing the scene and is accompanied by the Phantom
Scrooge is a man who is horrified by the actions of Joe and the others
Scrooge is a character who is observing a dark room and a dead man, feeling anxious and powerless in the presence of a Phantom
Scrooge is a character who is being guided by a ghost to witness various scenes
Scrooge is a character who interacts with the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come and learns about his future
Scrooge is the main character who undergoes a transformation after being visited by spirits
Scrooge is the main character who is experiencing a change of heart and generosity during Christmas Day
Scrooge is a central character who undergoes a transformation and becomes generous and kind
Scrooge is a character who undergoes a significant transformation, becoming generous and kind-hearted, especially towards Bob Cratchit and Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6,0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414,759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184,77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f,bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MARLEY">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Marley was Scrooge's business partner, who is now dead. He was as dead as a door-nail
Marley is Scrooge's former business partner who has been dead for seven years
Marley is Scrooge's deceased partner whose face appears on the knocker of Scrooge's door
Marley is a deceased individual whose face Scrooge remembers and who seems to haunt Scrooge
Marley is the ghost of Scrooge's former business partner, who appears to him dragging chains made of cash-boxes, keys, padlocks, ledgers, deeds, and heavy purses wrought in steel
Marley is mentioned as someone associated with Scrooge, possibly a former partner or acquaintance</data>
      <data key="d2">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414,759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184,77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TIM">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Tim is a character mentioned in the context of being someone's blood-horse</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ST. PAUL'S CHURCHYARD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">St. Paul's Churchyard is a location mentioned as a breezy spot</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="UNCLE SCROOGE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Uncle Scrooge is another reference to Scrooge, who came to dinner</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MARLEY'S FUNERAL">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Marley's Funeral is an event that confirmed Marley's death</data>
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCRATCH">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCROOGE'S NEPHEW">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Scrooge's nephew is a cheerful and warm-hearted individual who tries to spread Christmas cheer, despite Scrooge's negative attitude.
Scrooge's nephew is a cheerful and good-humored character who laughs heartily and expresses sympathy for Scrooge despite his ill whims
Scrooge's nephew is a cheerful and good-natured character who tries to include Scrooge in Christmas celebrations
Scrooge's nephew is the host of the game and the one who led the toast to Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d2">4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="COUNTING-HOUSE">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The counting-house is the office where Scrooge works, characterized by its cold and bleak environment.
The counting-house is the place where Scrooge and Jacob Marley conducted their business</data>
      <data key="d2">980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHRISTMAS EVE">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Christmas Eve is the day before Christmas, noted in the text as a significant time when Scrooge is busy in his counting-house.
Christmas Eve is the day before Christmas, celebrated by Bob Cratchit and mentioned in the context of Scrooge's disdain
Christmas Eve is mentioned as the time when Jacob Marley died seven years ago
Christmas Eve is the occasion during which Old Fezziwig hosts a lively and generous celebration, including dancing, food, and merriment</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CITY">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The city where Scrooge's counting-house is located, characterized by cold, bleak, and foggy weather.
The City is where Scrooge's business friends are located, who would be surprised to see his emotional state
A busy city where Scrooge and the Ghost observe the bustling Christmas-time activities
The city where Scrooge and the Spirit find themselves
The City is where Scrooge and the Phantom find themselves, particularly in the heart of it
The city where Scrooge lives and becomes known as a good man</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="NEIGHBOURING OFFICES">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">Offices near Scrooge's counting-house, where candles are flaring in the windows due to the dark and foggy weather.</data>
      <data key="d2">980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="COURT">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The court outside Scrooge's counting-house, where people are trying to warm themselves in the cold weather.
The corner of the court where the labourers are working and people are gathered around a fire</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CLERK">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1">
The clerk works for Scrooge and is sympathetic to the nephew's views on Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="NEPHEW">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The nephew is a character who tries to convince Scrooge of the goodness of Christmas and invites him to dine

Fred, who is Scrooge's nephew and welcomes him to dinner</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCROOGE AND MARLEY">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The business partnership between Scrooge and Marley
Scrooge and Marley is the counting-house or business where Scrooge works</data>
      <data key="d2">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
      <data key="d3">ORGANIZATION</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PORTLY GENTLEMEN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Two gentlemen who visit Scrooge's office to seek donations for charity</data>
      <data key="d2">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A holiday that Scrooge is cynical about but the nephew finds valuable and good
Christmas is a festive season during which people celebrate and make provisions for the poor and destitute
Christmas is a recurring event in the text, associated with Scrooge's memories and emotions
Christmas is the holiday during which many of the events in the text take place
Christmas is the holiday during which the events and reflections take place, symbolizing joy and reflection
Christmas is the holiday during which the events and reflections of Scrooge take place
Christmas is the holiday during which the events are taking place, and it is central to the appearance of the Ghost of Christmas Present
Christmas is the holiday during which the events are taking place, marked by festive activities and decorations
Christmas is the holiday being celebrated by the Cratchit family during their dinner
Christmas is the holiday being celebrated by various groups of people in the text
Christmas is the holiday being discussed, associated with kindness, festivities, and family gatherings
Christmas is the holiday being celebrated, which is central to the story and the characters' interactions
The holiday during which the events are taking place
</data>
      <data key="d2">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae,999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="UNION WORKHOUSES">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">Union workhouses are institutions where the poor and destitute are provided with basic necessities in exchange for labor</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TREADMILL">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Treadmill is a form of punishment and labor used in workhouses</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="POOR LAW">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Poor Law is legislation aimed at providing relief for the poor, often through workhouses</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LORD MAYOR">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Lord Mayor is a high-ranking official who oversees the city and has a household that celebrates Christmas in a grand manner</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MANSION HOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Mansion House is the official residence of the Lord Mayor</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ST. DUNSTAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">St. Dunstan is a historical figure known for his legendary battle with the Evil Spirit</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="EVIL SPIRIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Evil Spirit is a mythical figure who is said to have been defeated by St. Dunstan</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHRISTMAS CAROL">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A Christmas carol is a song sung during the Christmas season to spread cheer and goodwill
A song sung by a boy at Scrooge's door the previous night</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="POOR">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The poor and destitute individuals who suffer greatly and are in need of common necessities and comforts</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LABOURERS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Labourers who are repairing gas-pipes and warming themselves by a fire in the street</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="RAGGED MEN AND BOYS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A group of impoverished individuals gathered around a fire to keep warm</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LITTLE TAILOR">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A tailor who was fined by the Lord Mayor and is preparing for Christmas with his family</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LEAN WIFE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The wife of the little tailor, who is described as lean and is preparing for Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BABY">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The baby of the little tailor and his lean wife, who is part of the family preparing for Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHURCH">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">An ancient tower of a church with a gruff old bell that strikes the hours and quarters

The church is a place where people flock to in their best clothes and with their gayest faces
The place where Bob Cratchit and Tiny Tim went before returning home.</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MAIN STREET">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The main street where labourers are repairing gas-pipes and people are warming themselves by a fire</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GAS-PIPES">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The gas-pipes being repaired by labourers in the main street</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WATER-PLUG">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A water-plug left in solitude, whose overflowings have turned to ice</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SHOPS">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Shops with bright windows displaying holly sprigs and berries, making faces ruddy as people pass by</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="POULTERERS' AND GROCERS' TRADES">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Shops that are part of a splendid joke and a glorious pageant during the Christmas season</data>
      <data key="d2">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GENTLEMAN">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1">
</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CITY OF LONDON">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The City of London is the location where Scrooge resides and works</data>
      <data key="d2">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CAMDEN TOWN">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Camden Town is where Bob Cratchit runs home to play blind man's-buff
Camden Town is the location to which Scrooge plans to send the turkey</data>
      <data key="d2">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MARLEY'S FACE">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Marley's face appearing on the knocker is a supernatural event that startles Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d2">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CORNILL">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DUTCH MERCHANT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Dutch merchant is the person who built the old fireplace in Scrooge's house</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PHARAOH'S DAUGHTERS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Figures depicted on the Dutch tiles in Scrooge's fireplace</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="QUEENS OF SHEBA">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Figures depicted on the Dutch tiles in Scrooge's fireplace</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ANGELIC MESSENGERS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Figures depicted on the Dutch tiles in Scrooge's fireplace</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ABRAHAMS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Figures depicted on the Dutch tiles in Scrooge's fireplace</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BELSHAZZARS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Figures depicted on the Dutch tiles in Scrooge's fireplace</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="APOSTLES">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Figures depicted on the Dutch tiles in Scrooge's fireplace</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WINE-MERCHANT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The wine-merchant owns the cellar below Scrooge's house</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ACT OF PARLIAMENT">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A legislative act mentioned in a metaphor about the width of Scrooge's staircase</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HEARSE">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A vehicle for carrying a coffin, which Scrooge imagines going up his staircase</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GAS-LAMPS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Street lamps mentioned in the context of the darkness in Scrooge's house</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCRIPTURES">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Religious texts depicted on the Dutch tiles in Scrooge's fireplace</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PROPHET'S ROD">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A biblical reference used to describe Marley's face overshadowing other thoughts</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GHOSTS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Supernatural beings described as dragging chains in haunted houses</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HAUNTED HOUSES">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Houses believed to be inhabited by ghosts, mentioned in the context of Scrooge's experience</data>
      <data key="d2">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GHOST">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The supernatural occurrence of Marley's ghost appearing to Scrooge

A supernatural visitor that appears to Scrooge, described as a strange figure resembling both a child and an old man
The Ghost is a supernatural being guiding Scrooge through his past memories
The Ghost is a supernatural entity guiding Scrooge through his past experiences

The Ghost is a supernatural entity that guides Scrooge through his memories, prompting reflections and realizations
The Ghost is a supernatural being showing Scrooge scenes from his past
The Ghost is a supernatural entity that shows Scrooge visions of his past, present, and future
The Ghost is a spirit who tells Scrooge about Tiny Tim's potential future
The Ghost is a spirit who shows Scrooge visions of the future and rebukes him for his past behavior
The Ghost is a spirit guiding Scrooge through different scenes, spreading mirth and joy
The Ghost is a spirit accompanying Scrooge and showing him various scenes
</data>
      <data key="d2">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6,999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1">
Jacob Marley is a ghost who was once a business partner of Ebenezer Scrooge and now suffers in the afterlife for his earthly misdeeds
Jacob Marley is a ghost who appears to Scrooge to warn him about his fate and the visits of three spirits
Jacob Marley is a deceased partner of Scrooge who sends supernatural messengers to him
Jacob Marley is a deceased character whose memory haunts Scrooge, reminding him of his past
The ghost of Scrooge's former business partner who predicted the arrival of the spirits
Jacob Marley is the ghost of Scrooge's former business partner who warns him of the impending visits by spirits</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PHANTOM">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Phantom is another term used to describe the Ghost that visits Scrooge
Another name for the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come
The Phantom is a spirit guiding Scrooge through various scenes
The Phantom is a ghostly figure accompanying Scrooge
The Phantom is a ghostly figure that Scrooge glances towards
The Phantom is a ghostly figure pointing towards the head of a dead man, guiding Scrooge through a fearful experience</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WORLD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The world is referenced as the place where spirits wander after death if they did not do so in life</data>
      <data key="d2">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WARD">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Ward is mentioned as a figure who would have been justified in indicting the Ghost for making noise</data>
      <data key="d2">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </node>
    <node id="JACOB">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Jacob is a ghost who appears to Scrooge to warn him about his fate and the visits of three spirits
Jacob is Scrooge's old partner whose death is mentioned</data>
      <data key="d2">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Three Spirits are supernatural entities that will visit Scrooge to offer him a chance to change his fate</data>
      <data key="d2">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PHANTOMS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Phantoms are spirits seen by Scrooge, wandering in the air, wearing chains, and lamenting their inability to interfere in human matters</data>
      <data key="d2">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </node>
    <node id="NEIGHBOURING CHURCH">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A church near Scrooge's residence whose chimes are heard by Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d2">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="VISITATION">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The event warned by Marley's Ghost, where Scrooge is to be visited by another ghost when the bell tolls one</data>
      <data key="d2">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A supernatural entity that appears to Scrooge, described as a strange figure resembling both a child and an old man
Another term used to refer to the Ghost guiding Scrooge

The Spirit is a supernatural entity that guides Scrooge and teaches him lessons
The Spirit is a supernatural being who accompanies Scrooge and has the ability to sprinkle incense from his torch to restore good humor
The Spirit is another term used for the Ghost guiding Scrooge

A ghostly figure that shows Scrooge visions of the future and warns him about Ignorance and Want
The Spirit is another term used to refer to the Phantom guiding Scrooge

The Spirit is another term used for the Ghost guiding Scrooge
</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FIRST OF EXCHANGE">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A financial document mentioned by Scrooge, indicating a payment to be made to him</data>
      <data key="d2">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="COUNTRY ROAD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">An open country road with fields on either side where Scrooge and the Ghost of Christmas Past stand</data>
      <data key="d2">3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHRISTMAS PAST">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The period in Scrooge's life that the Ghost of Christmas Past is showing him</data>
      <data key="d2">3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MARKET-TOWN">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ALI BABA">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Ali Baba is a character from Arabian Nights, whom Scrooge recalls fondly from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="VALENTINE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Valentine is a character from Scrooge's childhood imagination, mentioned alongside his wild brother Orson</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ORSON">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Orson is a character from Scrooge's childhood imagination, mentioned alongside his brother Valentine</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DAMASCUS">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Damascus is a city mentioned in Scrooge's recollection of a story involving a character put down in his drawers at its gate</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SULTAN'S GROOM">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Sultan's Groom is a character from Scrooge's childhood imagination, turned upside down by the Genii</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GENII">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Genii are supernatural beings from Scrooge's childhood imagination, responsible for turning the Sultan's Groom upside down</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PRINCESS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Princess is a character from Scrooge's childhood imagination, mentioned in relation to the Sultan's Groom</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PARROT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Parrot is a character from Scrooge's childhood imagination, associated with Robin Crusoe</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ROBIN CRUSOE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Robin Crusoe is a character from Scrooge's childhood imagination, likely a reference to Robinson Crusoe</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FRIDAY">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Friday is a character from Scrooge's childhood imagination, likely a reference to Robinson Crusoe's companion</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HIGH-ROAD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The main road that Scrooge and the Ghost leave to approach the mansion</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LANE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A well-remembered lane that Scrooge and the Ghost travel down to reach the mansion</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="STABLES">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Part of the mansion's grounds, where fowls cluck and strut</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="COACH-HOUSES">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Part of the mansion's grounds, overrun with grass</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SHEDS">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Part of the mansion's grounds, overrun with grass</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HALL">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The dreary hall inside the mansion that Scrooge and the Ghost cross</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ROOM">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A long, bare, melancholy room in the mansion where Scrooge sees his younger self
The room is the setting where the matron and her children are gathered
The room where the dead man lies and where Scrooge and the Phantom are present</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="STOREHOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">An empty storehouse with an idle swinging door in the mansion's yard</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="YARD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The dull yard behind the mansion</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="POPPLAR">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A despondent poplar tree in the mansion's yard</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BOY">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A lonely boy reading near a feeble fire, representing Scrooge's younger self</data>
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MANSION">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCHOOLMASTER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The schoolmaster is a figure from Scrooge's past who interacts with him and his sister</data>
      <data key="d2">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WAREHOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The place where Scrooge was apprenticed and where Fezziwig worked
The warehouse is the place of business where Fezziwig, Ebenezer, and Dick Wilkins work and where the Christmas Eve celebration takes place</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </node>
    <node id="EBENEZER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Ebenezer is a former apprentice of Fezziwig, now grown into a young man, who is very much attached to his fellow apprentice, Dick Wilkins</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MISS FEZZIWIGS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The three Miss Fezziwigs are the daughters of Old Fezziwig, known for their beaming and lovable nature</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FIRUZABAD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Firuzabad held Aurelians as hostages</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="AURELIA">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Country seeking to release hostages</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="QUINTARA">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Country that negotiated a swap of money in exchange for hostages</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TIRUZIA">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Capital of Firuzabad where the Aurelians were being held</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="KROHAARA">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Capital city in Quintara</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CASHION">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Capital city in Aurelia</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SAMUEL NAMARA">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Aurelian who spent time in Tiruzia's Alhamia Prison</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ALHAMIA PRISON">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Prison in Tiruzia</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DURKE BATAGLANI">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Aurelian journalist who was held hostage</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MEGGIE TAZBAH">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Bratinas national and environmentalist who was held hostage</data>
      <data key="d2">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DICK">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Dick is one of the apprentices who praises Fezziwig and is part of Scrooge's past memories</data>
      <data key="d2">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FAIR YOUNG GIRL">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The fair young girl is a character who speaks to Scrooge about how his pursuit of wealth has displaced her in his affections</data>
      <data key="d2">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DOMESTIC BALL">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The domestic ball is an event hosted by Fezziwig where guests dance and celebrate, ending at eleven o'clock</data>
      <data key="d2">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
      <data key="d3">EVENT</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GIRL">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The girl is a character who was once in a relationship with Scrooge and is now a comely matron
The girl who answers the door at Fred's house and shows Scrooge upstairs</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MATERN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The matron is the same girl from Scrooge's past, now grown and with children</data>
      <data key="d2">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHILDREN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The children are the offspring of the matron, creating a tumultuous and lively scene
The children are characters who excitedly greet their father and interact with the Christmas toys and presents
The children of the mother, who are playing and whose voices she can hardly bear
The children of Bob Cratchit and Mrs. Cratchit, including Peter and Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WINTER FIRE">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The winter fire is a comforting element in the scene with the matron and her children</data>
      <data key="d2">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MOTHER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The mother is a character who sits with her husband and daughter by the fireside
A mother who is anxiously waiting for someone and is revealed by the Phantom to Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SECOND OF THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The second spirit is a supernatural entity that visits Scrooge after the first spirit</data>
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PARLOUR">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The parlour is a room in the house where the children and their emotions are described
The space behind the screen of rags in Old Joe's shop where the characters gather</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="OFFICE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The office is the place where Scrooge is seen by Belle's husband</data>
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BEDROOM">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The bedroom is where Scrooge finds himself after his encounter with the Ghost</data>
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FIRESIDE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The fireside is where the master of the house sits with his daughter and wife</data>
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FATHER">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MISTLETOE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Mistletoe is a type of plant with crisp leaves that reflect light, used as decoration in the room where the Ghost of Christmas Present appears</data>
      <data key="d2">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="IVY">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Ivy is a type of plant with crisp leaves that reflect light, used as decoration in the room where the Ghost of Christmas Present appears</data>
      <data key="d2">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PLENTY'S HORN">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Plenty's Horn is a symbolic reference to abundance, represented by the glowing torch held by the Ghost of Christmas Present</data>
      <data key="d2">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HOLLY">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GREAT BRITAIN">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Great Britain is the country where the events are taking place, characterized by a gloomy climate and town</data>
      <data key="d2">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PEOPLE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The people in the city are shoveling snow and engaging in festive activities on Christmas morning
</data>
      <data key="d2">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HOUSE-TOPS">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The house-tops are where people are shoveling snow and engaging in jovial activities</data>
      <data key="d2">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GROCER'S">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Grocer's is a shop nearly closed on Christmas morning, filled with various goods and festive items</data>
      <data key="d2">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="POULTERER'S">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Poulterer's is a shop that is half open on Christmas morning, selling poultry and other goods</data>
      <data key="d2">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FRUITERER'S">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Fruiterer's is a shop that is radiant with fruits and other goods on Christmas morning</data>
      <data key="d2">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CITY STREETS">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Christmas Day is the occasion being celebrated, during which people are seen carrying their dinners to the bakers' shops
Christmas Day is the day on which the events in the Cratchit household take place. It is a significant day for the family, filled with joy, surprises, and a festive meal.

Christmas Day is the holiday that Scrooge wakes up to after his transformative experience with the spirits
Christmas Day is the holiday being celebrated, which is central to the events in the text</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHAPEL">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The chapel is another place where people flock to in their best clothes and with their gayest faces</data>
      <data key="d2">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BAKER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The baker is a character who shuts up his shop after the bells cease, and the progress of the dinners' cooking is seen in the thawed blotch of wet above each baker's oven</data>
      <data key="d2">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BOB CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Bob Cratchit's dwelling is a modest four-roomed house that the Spirit blesses with the sprinklings of his torch</data>
      <data key="d2">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GROCER">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CUSTOMERS">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DINNER-CARRIERS">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MASTER PETER CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Master Peter Cratchit is the son and heir of Bob Cratchit. He is described as wearing a monstrous shirt-collar and is eager to show off his attire. He helps with the meal by mashing the potatoes.</data>
      <data key="d2">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Tiny Tim is the youngest son of Bob Cratchit. He is a cripple who uses a little crutch and has his limbs supported by an iron frame. Despite his condition, he is thoughtful and hopeful, wishing to inspire others.
Tiny Tim is a young member of the Cratchit family who is frail and sits beside his father, Bob Cratchit
Tiny Tim is a child who is ill and whose future is uncertain
Tiny Tim is the deceased child of Bob Cratchit and Mrs. Cratchit
Tiny Tim is a child who is remembered fondly by Bob and his family
Tiny Tim is Bob Cratchit's son, who is mentioned in comparison to the size of the turkey
Tiny Tim is a young boy who is part of Bob Cratchit's family and is shown to be alive and well after Scrooge's transformation</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WASH-HOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The place where Tiny Tim was taken by his siblings to hear the pudding singing in the copper.</data>
      <data key="d2">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MASTER PETER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Master Peter is a member of the Cratchit family who mashed the potatoes with incredible vigor</data>
      <data key="d2">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MISS BELINDA">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Miss Belinda is a member of the Cratchit family who sweetened the apple sauce and changed the plates</data>
      <data key="d2">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MARTHA">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Martha is a member of the Cratchit family who dusted the hot plates</data>
      <data key="d2">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DINNER">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The dinner is the meal prepared and enjoyed by the Cratchit family, featuring a goose and pudding</data>
      <data key="d2">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FOUNDER OF THE FEAST">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A title given to Scrooge by Bob Cratchit, albeit sarcastically</data>
      <data key="d2">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MINERS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Miners are people who live on a bleak and desert moor and are seen celebrating Christmas in a hut</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LIGHTHOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A solitary lighthouse built on a dismal reef of sunken rocks, where two men are celebrating Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SHIP">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A ship far away from any shore, where the crew is celebrating Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HUT">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A hut on the bleak and desert moor where miners and their families are celebrating Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SEA">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The sea that Scrooge and the Ghost travel over, encountering a lighthouse and a ship</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="OLD MAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">An old man in the hut who sings a Christmas song to his family</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LAMPLIGHTER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A lamplighter who laughs as the Spirit passes by</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TWO MEN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Two men who watch the light in the lighthouse and celebrate Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CREW">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The crew of the ship who celebrate Christmas</data>
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BLEAK AND DESERT MOOR">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCROOGE'S NIECE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Scrooge's niece is described as exceedingly pretty, earnest, and opinionated, particularly about Scrooge's wealth and behavior
Scrooge's niece is a musical character who plays the harp and participates in the games</data>
      <data key="d2">4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TOPPER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Topper is a character who is a bachelor and has his eye on one of Scrooge's niece's sisters
Topper is a character who is part of the musical family and participates in the games, particularly blind man's-buff
Topper is a character who could have told you about the sharp girls at the gathering
Topper is a guest at Fred's dinner party</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCROOGE'S NIECE'S SISTER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Scrooge's niece's sister is the plump one with the lace tucker who blushes when Topper expresses his opinion</data>
      <data key="d2">bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PLUMP SISTER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The plump sister is a character who participates in the games and is often pursued by Topper during blind man's-buff
The plump sister is another guest at Fred's dinner party</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6</data>
      <data key="d3">PERSON</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LONDON">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">London is the city where the story takes place and where the animal in the guessing game lives</data>
      <data key="d2">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TWELFTH-NIGHT PARTY">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">A children's party that Scrooge and the Spirit visited during their travels</data>
      <data key="d2">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHRISTMAS HOLIDAYS">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Christmas holidays are the time period during which Scrooge and the Spirit travel together</data>
      <data key="d2">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ALMSHOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">An almshouse is one of the places visited by the Spirit and Scrooge, where they observed cheerfulness despite poverty</data>
      <data key="d2">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HOSPITAL">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A hospital is one of the places visited by the Spirit and Scrooge, where they observed cheerfulness despite illness</data>
      <data key="d2">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GAOL">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A gaol (jail) is one of the places visited by the Spirit and Scrooge, where they observed cheerfulness despite imprisonment</data>
      <data key="d2">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </node>
    <node id="IGNORANCE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A boy representing ignorance, shown to Scrooge by the Spirit</data>
      <data key="d2">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WANT">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A girl representing want, shown to Scrooge by the Spirit</data>
      <data key="d2">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </node>
    <node id="OLD JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The ghost of Scrooge's former business partner who predicted the arrival of the spirits</data>
      <data key="d2">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHANGE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The location in the city where merchants gather
Change is a location within the City where merchants gather</data>
      <data key="d2">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BUSINESS MEN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Business men are wealthy and important individuals in the City who discuss the death of an unknown person</data>
      <data key="d2">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="RED-FACED GENTLEMAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A red-faced gentleman with a pendulous excrescence on his nose who discusses the death of an unknown person</data>
      <data key="d2">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GREAT FAT MAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A great fat man with a monstrous chin who discusses the death of an unknown person</data>
      <data key="d2">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="OLD SCRATCH">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Old Scratch is a colloquial term used to refer to the Devil, mentioned by the business men</data>
      <data key="d2">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MERCHANTS">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="OLD JOE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Old Joe is a grey-haired rascal who owns a shop dealing in second-hand goods</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LAUNDRESS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The laundress is a woman who enters Old Joe's shop with a heavy bundle</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </node>
    <node id="UNDERTAKER'S MAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The undertaker's man is a man in faded black who enters Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </node>
    <node id="TOWN">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">An obscure part of the town with a bad reputation where Scrooge and the Phantom visit
The town where Scrooge asks the Spirit to show him someone who feels emotion caused by the man's death</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SHOP">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A low-browed, beetling shop owned by Old Joe where second-hand goods are bought and sold</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </node>
    <node id="INFAMOUS RESORT">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">An infamous part of the town known for its bad reputation, where Old Joe's shop is located</data>
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHARWOMAN">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </node>
    <node id="UNHAPPY MAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The deceased man whose belongings are being plundered and discussed by Joe and the others</data>
      <data key="d2">bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WOMAN">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DEATH">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The event of a man's death, which is causing various emotions and reactions among the characters</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CAROLINE'S HUSBAND">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Caroline's husband is a young man with a careworn and depressed face, who brings the news of the creditor's death</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CREDITOR">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">A merciless creditor whose death brings relief to Caroline and her husband
The merciless creditor whose death brings relief to Caroline and her family</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The dark, empty house where the dead man lies</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BED">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The bed on which the dead man lies</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HEARTHSTONE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The location beneath which rats are gnawing in the room of death</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="DOOR">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The door that the cat is tearing at in the room of death</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WINDOW">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The window from which the mother looks out anxiously</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CLOCK">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The clock that the mother glances at while waiting</data>
      <data key="d2">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PETER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Peter is one of the Cratchit children
Peter is a character who interacts with Bob and is mentioned in relation to getting a better situation</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MR. SCROOGE'S NEPHEW">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Mr. Scrooge's nephew is a kind gentleman who offers help to Bob Cratchit</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BOB CRATCHIT'S HOUSE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The house where Bob Cratchit and his family live</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FIRE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The place around which the Cratchit family gathers</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BOOK">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The book that Peter is reading</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="THRESHOLD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The entrance to Bob Cratchit's house</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHAIR">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The chair set close beside Tiny Tim's body</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="HOB">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The place where Bob Cratchit's tea is kept warm</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="STREET">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The street where Mr. Scrooge's nephew meets Bob Cratchit</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SUNDAY">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The day Bob Cratchit promises to visit Tiny Tim's grave</data>
      <data key="d2">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="BOB">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Bob is a character who speaks about his good wife and Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="CHURCHYARD">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">A place where Scrooge sees the grave with his name on it</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SCROOGE'S OFFICE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The place where Scrooge works and sees a different figure in the chair</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="IRON GATE">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The gate that Scrooge and the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come pass through before entering the churchyard</data>
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SPIRIT OF TINY TIM">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS FUTURE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The Ghost of Christmas Future, also known as the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come, shows Scrooge the potential future consequences of his actions</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PAST">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Past is one of the time periods that Scrooge vows to honor and learn from after his transformative experience</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PRESENT">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Present is one of the time periods that Scrooge vows to honor and learn from after his transformative experience</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FUTURE">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The Future is one of the time periods that Scrooge vows to honor and learn from after his transformative experience</data>
      <data key="d2">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PORTLY GENTLEMAN">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The portly gentleman is a character who had previously visited Scrooge's counting-house to ask for donations</data>
      <data key="d2">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="LAD">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The lad is the boy who Scrooge asks to buy the turkey and bring it to him</data>
      <data key="d2">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="JOE MILLER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Joe Miller is mentioned in comparison to the joke of sending the turkey to Bob Cratchit</data>
      <data key="d2">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="POULTERER">
      <data key="d0" />
      <data key="d1" />
      <data key="d2">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="NIECE BY MARRIAGE">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Fred's wife, who is surprised by Scrooge's arrival at the dinner party</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MISTRESS">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Fred's wife, who is in the dining room when Scrooge arrives</data>
      <data key="d2">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45</data>
    </node>
    <node id="ILLUSTRATION">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">Illustration is a visual representation included in the text to depict scenes from the story</data>
      <data key="d2">2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PROJECT GUTENBERG LITERARY ARCHIVE FOUNDATION">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation owns a compilation copyright in the collection of Project Gutenberg electronic works
The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation (PGLAF) owns a compilation copyright in the collection of Project Gutenberg&#8482; electronic works and promotes free access to electronic works
The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation manages the Project Gutenberg trademark and handles royalty payments and permissions
The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation is a non-profit 501(c)(3) educational corporation organized under the laws of Mississippi. It was created in 2001 to provide a secure and permanent future for Project Gutenberg and its mission.</data>
      <data key="d2">0ddc17ea5e566006c000b4013f2181a5,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa,cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="WWW.GUTENBERG.ORG">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The official website of Project Gutenberg where the full Project Gutenberg License can be found</data>
      <data key="d2">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PROJECT GUTENBERG LICENSE">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The license that governs the use, distribution, and modification of Project Gutenberg works</data>
      <data key="d2">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </node>
    <node id="COPYRIGHT HOLDER">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">The individual or entity that holds the copyright to a specific Project Gutenberg work</data>
      <data key="d2">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </node>
    <node id="COUNTRY">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Any country outside the United States where different copyright laws may apply to Project Gutenberg works</data>
      <data key="d2">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PROJECT GUTENBERG&#8482; TRADEMARK">
      <data key="d0">EVENT</data>
      <data key="d1">The trademark associated with Project Gutenberg works</data>
      <data key="d2">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </node>
    <node id="U.S.">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">The United States, where Project Gutenberg conducts copyright research and transcribes works not protected by copyright law</data>
      <data key="d2">0ddc17ea5e566006c000b4013f2181a5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="FOUNDATION">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Foundation refers to the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation, which manages the Project Gutenberg trademark and handles royalty payments and permissions
</data>
      <data key="d2">0ddc17ea5e566006c000b4013f2181a5,cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MICHAEL S. HART">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Professor Michael S. Hart was the originator of the Project Gutenberg concept, creating a library of electronic works that could be freely shared with anyone. He produced and distributed Project Gutenberg eBooks for forty years with the support of volunteers.</data>
      <data key="d2">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="SALT LAKE CITY">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Salt Lake City is the location of the business office of the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation.</data>
      <data key="d2">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="MISSISSIPPI">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Mississippi is the state under whose laws the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation is organized.</data>
      <data key="d2">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="INTERNAL REVENUE SERVICE">
      <data key="d0">ORGANIZATION</data>
      <data key="d1">The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) is the U.S. government agency that granted tax-exempt status to the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation.</data>
      <data key="d2">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="UTAH">
      <data key="d0">GEO</data>
      <data key="d1">Utah is the state where the business office of the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation is located, specifically in Salt Lake City.</data>
      <data key="d2">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="PROFESSOR MICHAEL S. HART">
      <data key="d0">PERSON</data>
      <data key="d1">Professor Michael S. Hart was the originator of the Project Gutenberg concept, creating a library of electronic works that could be freely shared with anyone. He produced and distributed Project Gutenberg eBooks for forty years with the support of volunteers.</data>
      <data key="d2">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </node>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="UNITED STATES">
      <data key="d4">5.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Project Gutenberg is based in the United States
Project Gutenberg distributes electronic works in the United States
Most of the works in Project Gutenberg are in the public domain in the United States
Project Gutenberg operates within the United States and complies with its laws.</data>
      <data key="d6">2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa,cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="A CHRISTMAS CAROL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Project Gutenberg distributes 'A Christmas Carol' as part of its collection</data>
      <data key="d6">2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="PROJECT GUTENBERG LITERARY ARCHIVE FOUNDATION">
      <data key="d4">6.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation owns the compilation copyright of Project Gutenberg's electronic works
The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation owns the compilation copyright of Project Gutenberg's electronic works
The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation manages the Project Gutenberg trademark and handles royalty payments and permissions
The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation was created to support and secure the future of Project Gutenberg.</data>
      <data key="d6">0ddc17ea5e566006c000b4013f2181a5,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa,cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="WWW.GUTENBERG.ORG">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The official website of Project Gutenberg where users can find the full Project Gutenberg License</data>
      <data key="d6">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="PROJECT GUTENBERG LICENSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Project Gutenberg License governs the use, distribution, and modification of Project Gutenberg works</data>
      <data key="d6">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="COPYRIGHT HOLDER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Some Project Gutenberg works are posted with the permission of the copyright holder</data>
      <data key="d6">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="COUNTRY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Users outside the United States must check the copyright laws of their country before using Project Gutenberg works</data>
      <data key="d6">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="PROJECT GUTENBERG&#8482; TRADEMARK">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Project Gutenberg&#8482; trademark is associated with Project Gutenberg works</data>
      <data key="d6">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="U.S.">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Project Gutenberg conducts copyright research and transcribes works not protected by U.S. copyright law</data>
      <data key="d6">0ddc17ea5e566006c000b4013f2181a5</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="MICHAEL S. HART">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Michael S. Hart was the originator of the Project Gutenberg concept and produced its eBooks for forty years.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="FOUNDATION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Foundation supports Project Gutenberg by providing a secure and permanent future for its mission.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG" target="PROFESSOR MICHAEL S. HART">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Professor Michael S. Hart was the originator of the Project Gutenberg concept and produced its eBooks for forty years.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHARLES DICKENS" target="A CHRISTMAS CAROL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Charles Dickens is the author of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="ARTHUR RACKHAM" target="A CHRISTMAS CAROL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Arthur Rackham is the illustrator of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="J. B. LIPPINCOTT COMPANY" target="A CHRISTMAS CAROL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">J. B. Lippincott Company is the original publisher of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="UNITED STATES" target="FOUNDATION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Foundation complies with charity laws in all 50 states of the United States.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="SUZANNE SHELL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Suzanne Shell is one of the producers of the Project Gutenberg eBook of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="JANET BLENKINSHIP">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Janet Blenkinship is one of the producers of the Project Gutenberg eBook of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="ONLINE DISTRIBUTED PROOFREADING TEAM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Online Distributed Proofreading Team helped produce the Project Gutenberg eBook of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="PHILADELPHIA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Philadelphia is one of the cities where "A Christmas Carol" was originally published</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="NEW YORK">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">New York is one of the cities where "A Christmas Carol" was originally published</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="MARLEY'S GHOST">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Marley's Ghost is the first chapter of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="THE FIRST OF THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The First of the Three Spirits is the second chapter of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="THE SECOND OF THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Second of the Three Spirits is the third chapter of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="THE LAST OF THE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Last of the Spirits is the fourth chapter of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="A CHRISTMAS CAROL" target="THE END OF IT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The End of It is the fifth and final chapter of "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="EBENEZER SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit is the clerk to Ebenezer Scrooge in "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="PETER CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Peter Cratchit is the son of Bob Cratchit in "A Christmas Carol"
Peter Cratchit is Bob Cratchit's son</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="TIM CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tim Cratchit, also known as Tiny Tim, is the youngest son of Bob Cratchit in "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="MRS. CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">5.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit is the wife of Bob Cratchit in "A Christmas Carol"
Mrs. Cratchit is Bob Cratchit's wife
Bob Cratchit and Mrs. Cratchit are husband and wife, working together to support their family.
Mrs. Cratchit and Bob Cratchit are married and part of the Cratchit family
Bob Cratchit is married to Mrs. Cratchit</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="BELINDA CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Belinda Cratchit is a daughter of Bob Cratchit in "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="MARTHA CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha Cratchit is a daughter of Bob Cratchit in "A Christmas Carol"
Martha Cratchit is Bob Cratchit's daughter</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">7.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is Bob Cratchit's employer and is reluctant to give him a day off on Christmas Eve
Bob Cratchit is Scrooge's clerk
Bob Cratchit works for Scrooge
Scrooge is observing Bob Cratchit's family
Scrooge plans to send a large turkey to Bob Cratchit as a surprise gift
Scrooge is Bob Cratchit's employer and decides to raise his salary and assist his family
Scrooge promises to raise Bob Cratchit's salary and assist his struggling family</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CAMDEN TOWN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit runs home to Camden Town to play blind man's-buff</data>
      <data key="d6">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CHRISTMAS EVE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit celebrates Christmas Eve by sliding on Cornhill and running home</data>
      <data key="d6">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CORNILL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit slides on Cornhill in celebration of Christmas Eve</data>
      <data key="d6">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit blesses Bob Cratchit's house with the sprinklings of his torch</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Present blesses Bob Cratchit's house
The Ghost of Christmas Present blesses Bob Cratchit's house, showing a supernatural connection to the Cratchit family.</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="BOB CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit lives in a modest four-roomed house</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">4.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit is the father of Tiny Tim and is very caring towards him, carrying him on his shoulder and being concerned about his health.
Bob Cratchit is Tiny Tim's father and shows great affection and concern for him
Tiny Tim is Bob Cratchit's son
Bob Cratchit is the father of Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Christmas Day is significant for Bob Cratchit as it is the day he spends with his family, filled with joy and celebration.
Bob Cratchit celebrates Christmas Day with his family</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit lives in the Cratchit dwelling with his family.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CHURCH">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit took Tiny Tim to the church before returning home.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit is a member of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit is celebrating Christmas with his family
The events are taking place during Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="DINNER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit is participating in the family dinner</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="PETER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit is the father of Peter</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="MR. SCROOGE'S NEPHEW">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mr. Scrooge's nephew offers help to Bob Cratchit</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="BOB CRATCHIT'S HOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit lives in this house with his family</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CHILDREN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit is the father of the children</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="FIRE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Cratchit family gathers around the fire</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="CHAIR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit sits in the chair beside Tiny Tim's body</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="HOB">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit's tea is kept warm on the hob</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="STREET">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit meets Mr. Scrooge's nephew in the street</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BOB CRATCHIT" target="SUNDAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob Cratchit promises to visit Tiny Tim's grave on Sunday</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="FRED">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fred is the nephew of Ebenezer Scrooge in "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="GHOST OF JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Jacob Marley is the spectre of Scrooge's former partner in business in "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="FAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fan is the sister of Scrooge in "A Christmas Carol"</data>
      <data key="d6">d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob Marley, as a ghost, visits Ebenezer Scrooge to warn him about the consequences of his actions
Jacob Marley appears to Scrooge to warn him about his fate and the visits of three spirits</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="GHOST">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost visits Ebenezer Scrooge to warn him about the consequences of his actions
The Ghost appears to Scrooge and is described in detail</data>
      <data key="d6">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6,e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="PHANTOM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Phantom, another term for the Ghost, interacts with Ebenezer Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="COUNTING-HOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The counting-house is where Scrooge and Jacob Marley conducted their business</data>
      <data key="d6">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="MARLEY'S GHOST">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Marley's Ghost is the apparition of Jacob Marley, who warns Scrooge about his fate and the visits of three spirits
Marley's Ghost haunts Scrooge and warns him of future visitations</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Three Spirits will visit Scrooge to offer him a chance to change his fate</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="THE FIRST OF THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The First of the Three Spirits will visit Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="VISITATION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is warned by Marley's Ghost about a visitation</data>
      <data key="d6">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="NEIGHBOURING CHURCH">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge hears the chimes of the neighbouring church</data>
      <data key="d6">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="CHURCH">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge hears the chimes of the neighbouring church</data>
      <data key="d6">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit appears to Scrooge and is described in detail</data>
      <data key="d6">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="FIRST OF EXCHANGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge mentions the First of Exchange as a financial document</data>
      <data key="d6">8435b078474636a989a8c22f5493e1b6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="EBENEZER SCROOGE" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge reads his own name, Ebenezer Scrooge, on a neglected grave</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PETER CRATCHIT" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Peter Cratchit celebrates Christmas Day with his family</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MR. FEZZIWIG" target="MRS. FEZZIWIG">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Fezziwig is the worthy partner of Mr. Fezziwig in "A Christmas Carol"
Mr. Fezziwig and Mrs. Fezziwig are partners in dancing and hosts of the domestic ball</data>
      <data key="d6">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,d6583840046247f428a9f02738842a7c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MR. FEZZIWIG" target="DOMESTIC BALL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mr. Fezziwig hosts the domestic ball, spreading cheer among the guests</data>
      <data key="d6">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FRED" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">4.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fred invited his uncle Scrooge to dinner
Fred is Scrooge's nephew and expresses sympathy for him despite his unpleasant nature
Fred is Scrooge's nephew and hosted the game where Scrooge was the subject
Scrooge is Fred's uncle and is warmly welcomed to dinner</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FRED" target="UNCLE SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Uncle Scrooge is invited to dinner by Fred</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FRED" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fred enjoys Christmas and finds it a time for laughter and good-humor</data>
      <data key="d6">bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FRED" target="TOPPER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Topper is a guest at Fred's dinner party</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FRED" target="PLUMP SISTER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The plump sister is a guest at Fred's dinner party</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PAST" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">7.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Past visits Scrooge to show him scenes from his past for his reclamation
The Ghost of Christmas Past guides Scrooge through his memories
The Ghost of Christmas Past shows Scrooge scenes from his past
The Ghost of Christmas Past shows Scrooge scenes from his past
The Ghost of Christmas Past shows Scrooge scenes from his past</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PAST" target="CHRISTMAS PAST">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Past is associated with the period of Christmas Past</data>
      <data key="d6">3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">7.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Present appears to Scrooge to show him the spirit of the holiday
Scrooge is guided by the Ghost of Christmas Present
The Ghost of Christmas Present shows Scrooge scenes from the present
The Ghost of Christmas Present shows Scrooge the current state of affairs and introduces him to Ignorance and Want
The Ghost of Christmas Present shows Scrooge the current state of his life and the lives of others
Scrooge recalls seeing people with the Ghost of Christmas Present</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a,77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Present embodies the spirit of the Christmas holiday</data>
      <data key="d6">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="HOLLY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Holly is part of the festive decorations surrounding the Ghost of Christmas Present</data>
      <data key="d6">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="MISTLETOE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mistletoe is part of the festive decorations surrounding the Ghost of Christmas Present</data>
      <data key="d6">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="IVY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Ivy is part of the festive decorations surrounding the Ghost of Christmas Present</data>
      <data key="d6">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="PLENTY'S HORN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Present holds a glowing torch shaped like Plenty's Horn</data>
      <data key="d6">77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Present is a specific form of the Spirit
The Spirit is also referred to as the Ghost of Christmas Present</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PRESENT" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Present is associated with Christmas Day, spreading joy and blessings.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS YET TO COME" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">4.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come shows Scrooge the future
Scrooge is shown visions of the future by the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come
The Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come shows Scrooge the potential future consequences of his actions</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST OF JACOB MARLEY" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Jacob Marley warns Scrooge about the visits from the three spirits</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="JOE" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Joe discussed bed-curtains with a woman, which is related to Scrooge's story</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="JOE" target="MRS. DILBER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Joe appraises and buys items brought by Mrs. Dilber</data>
      <data key="d6">bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="JOE" target="WOMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Joe appraises and buys items brought by the woman</data>
      <data key="d6">bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="JOE" target="UNHAPPY MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Joe appraises and buys items that were taken from the unhappy man</data>
      <data key="d6">bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="DICK WILKINS" target="FEZZIWIG">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fezziwig is the former employer of Dick Wilkins, and they share a warm relationship, especially evident during the Christmas Eve celebration</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="DICK WILKINS" target="EBENEZER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Ebenezer and Dick Wilkins were fellow apprentices and shared a close bond</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="DICK WILKINS" target="WAREHOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Dick Wilkins works at the warehouse and participates in the Christmas Eve celebration</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BELLE" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Belle is an old friend of Scrooge, and her husband mentions seeing Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BELLE" target="FATHER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Belle is the wife of the father</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BELLE" target="FIRESIDE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Belle sits with her husband and mother by the fireside</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CAROLINE" target="CAROLINE'S HUSBAND">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Caroline and her husband discuss the death of the creditor and its implications</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CAROLINE" target="CREDITOR">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Caroline feels relief upon hearing about the death of the merciless creditor
Caroline feels relief at the death of the merciless creditor</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CAROLINE" target="TOWN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Caroline and her husband live in the town where the creditor's death has an impact</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="BELINDA CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit and Belinda Cratchit are mother and daughter, working together to prepare the family meal.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="MASTER PETER CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit and Master Peter Cratchit are mother and son, with Peter helping in the kitchen by mashing the potatoes.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="MARTHA CRATCHIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit and Martha Cratchit are mother and daughter, with Mrs. Cratchit warmly welcoming Martha when she arrives home.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit lives in the Cratchit dwelling with her family.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="MASTER PETER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter is a member of the Cratchit family and helps with the dinner preparations</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="MISS BELINDA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Miss Belinda is a member of the Cratchit family and helps with the dinner preparations</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="MARTHA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha is a member of the Cratchit family and helps with the dinner preparations</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim is a member of the Cratchit family and part of the dinner scene
Mrs. Cratchit is the mother of Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit is a member of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit is celebrating Christmas with her family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="DINNER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit is participating in the family dinner</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit strongly dislikes Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit celebrates Christmas Day with her family</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="PETER">
      <data key="d4">3.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit is the mother of Peter
Mrs. Cratchit speaks to Peter about his future</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="CHILDREN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Cratchit is the mother of the children</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. CRATCHIT" target="BOB">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob and Mrs. Cratchit are married and interact with each otherMrs. Cratchit is Bob's wife and interacts with him</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BELINDA CRATCHIT" target="CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Belinda Cratchit lives in the Cratchit dwelling with her family.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARTHA CRATCHIT" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha Cratchit and Tiny Tim are siblings, with Martha hiding to surprise her father and being part of the family celebration.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARTHA CRATCHIT" target="CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha Cratchit lives in the Cratchit dwelling with her family.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARTHA CRATCHIT" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha Cratchit celebrates Christmas Day with her family</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. DILBER" target="OLD JOE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Dilber interacts with Old Joe in his shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. DILBER" target="LAUNDRESS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Dilber and the laundress meet in Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. DILBER" target="UNDERTAKER'S MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Dilber and the undertaker's man meet in Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. DILBER" target="PARLOUR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Dilber enters the parlour</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. DILBER" target="CHARWOMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The charwoman and Mrs. Dilber meet in Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FAN" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fan is Scrooge's sister who comes to bring him home for Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FAN" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fan brings Scrooge home for Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. FEZZIWIG" target="FEZZIWIG">
      <data key="d4">3.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Old Fezziwig and Mrs. Fezziwig danced together
Fezziwig and Mrs. Fezziwig are married and both participate in the Christmas Eve festivities
Fezziwig and Mrs. Fezziwig are partners in dancing and hosts of the domestic ball</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. FEZZIWIG" target="CHRISTMAS EVE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Fezziwig participates in the Christmas Eve celebration hosted by Fezziwig</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MRS. FEZZIWIG" target="WAREHOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Mrs. Fezziwig participates in the Christmas Eve celebration at the warehouse</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="THE FIRST OF THE THREE SPIRITS" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The First of the Three Spirits will visit Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARLEY'S GHOST" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">3.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Marley's Ghost is an event that involves Scrooge
Scrooge is confronted by the ghost of Marley, which he initially disbelieves
Marley's Ghost is the apparition of Jacob Marley, who warns Scrooge about his fate and the visits of three spirits</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARLEY'S GHOST" target="THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Marley's Ghost informs Scrooge about the visits of the Three Spirits</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FEZZIWIG" target="SCROOGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fezziwig was Scrooge's employer during his apprenticeship</data>
      <data key="d6">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FEZZIWIG" target="WAREHOUSE">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fezziwig worked at the warehouse where Scrooge was apprenticed
Fezziwig runs the warehouse where the Christmas Eve celebration takes place</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FEZZIWIG" target="EBENEZER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fezziwig is the former employer of Ebenezer, and they share a warm relationship, especially evident during the Christmas Eve celebration</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FEZZIWIG" target="MISS FEZZIWIGS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fezziwig is the father of the three Miss Fezziwigs, who are known for their beaming and lovable nature</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FEZZIWIG" target="CHRISTMAS EVE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fezziwig hosts a lively and generous celebration on Christmas Eve</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FEZZIWIG" target="GHOST">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge speaks to the Ghost about Fezziwig, showing his fond memories of his former employer</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FEZZIWIG" target="DOMESTIC BALL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fezziwig hosts the domestic ball, spreading cheer among the guests</data>
      <data key="d6">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">8.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and Marley were business partners, and Scrooge was Marley's sole executor
Marley was Scrooge's business partner who has been dead for seven years
Marley was Scrooge's deceased partner whose face appears on the knocker
Scrooge is haunted by the memory and face of Marley, who has been dead for seven years
Marley was Scrooge's business partner in life and now appears to him as a ghost
Marley is mentioned in relation to Scrooge, indicating a past connection</data>
      <data key="d6">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1,7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414,759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184,77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="TIM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tim is mentioned in the context of Scrooge's story</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SCRATCH">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Old Scratch is mentioned in a conversation related to Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="MARLEY'S FUNERAL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge attended Marley's Funeral and was his sole executor</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SCROOGE'S NEPHEW">
      <data key="d4">5.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge's nephew tries to engage with Scrooge and spread Christmas cheer, despite Scrooge's negative attitude towards Christmas
Scrooge's nephew is related to Scrooge and expresses sympathy for him despite his unpleasant nature
Scrooge's nephew tries to include Scrooge in Christmas celebrations despite Scrooge's dislike for the holiday
Scrooge's nephew hosted the game and led the toast to Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="COUNTING-HOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge works in the counting-house, which reflects his cold and unfeeling nature</data>
      <data key="d6">980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHRISTMAS EVE">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is busy working in his counting-house on Christmas Eve, showing his disregard for the holiday
Scrooge is reluctant to give Bob Cratchit a day off on Christmas Eve</data>
      <data key="d6">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CLERK">
      <data key="d4">3.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The clerk works for Scrooge and suffers from the cold environment in the counting-house
The clerk works for Scrooge and shares the nephew's positive views on Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CITY">
      <data key="d4">6.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge lives and works in the city, which is described as cold, bleak, and foggy
Scrooge's business friends in the City would be surprised to see his emotional state
Scrooge and the Ghost observe the bustling activities in the city during Christmas
Scrooge and the Spirit find themselves in the heart of the City
Scrooge and the Phantom are in the City
Scrooge becomes known as a good man in the city</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="NEIGHBOURING OFFICES">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The neighbouring offices are near Scrooge's counting-house, and their candles are visible through the fog</data>
      <data key="d6">980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="COURT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The court is outside Scrooge's counting-house, where people are trying to warm themselves</data>
      <data key="d6">980594a50d68db06e6ca257bdb9ae95e</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="NEPHEW">
      <data key="d4">4.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is the uncle of the nephew, and they have differing views on Christmas
Scrooge's nephew is the child of his sister Fan
Scrooge is welcomed by his nephew Fred to the dinner party</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SCROOGE AND MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">3.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is the surviving partner of the business Scrooge and Marley
Scrooge works at Scrooge and Marley, the counting-house</data>
      <data key="d6">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="PORTLY GENTLEMEN">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The portly gentlemen visit Scrooge to seek donations for charity</data>
      <data key="d6">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">15.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is cynical about Christmas and expresses his disdain for it
Scrooge is notably uncharitable during the Christmas season
Scrooge has complex emotions and memories associated with Christmas
Many of Scrooge's past experiences and reflections are centered around Christmas
Scrooge's reflections and interactions with the Ghost take place during Christmas
The events and reflections of Scrooge take place during Christmas
Scrooge is experiencing supernatural events related to the Christmas holiday
Scrooge's experiences and lessons are centered around the Christmas holiday
Scrooge has a negative opinion about Christmas, calling it a humbug
Scrooge has a complex relationship with Christmas, initially disliking it but gradually softening
Scrooge is observing events during Christmas
Scrooge learns to keep Christmas well and becomes generous</data>
      <data key="d6">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74,0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,77ae3762a0b062ca5350ea54a05450ae,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="UNION WORKHOUSES">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge supports the Union workhouses as a means to provide for the poor</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="TREADMILL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge mentions the Treadmill as a form of punishment and labor for the poor</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="POOR LAW">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge references the Poor Law as a means to support the poor</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHRISTMAS CAROL">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge reacts negatively to a Christmas carol sung at his keyhole
Scrooge recalls a boy singing a Christmas carol at his door</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GENTLEMAN">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The gentleman approaches Scrooge to ask for donations for the poor
Scrooge interacts with the gentleman and surprises him with his generosity</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHURCH">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The church's bell strikes the hours and quarters, which Scrooge can hear</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CITY OF LONDON">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge lives and works in the City of London</data>
      <data key="d6">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="MARLEY'S FACE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is startled by the appearance of Marley's face on the knocker</data>
      <data key="d6">7064df4af064aeb556e5bab52e896414</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="DUTCH MERCHANT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Dutch merchant built the old fireplace in Scrooge's house</data>
      <data key="d6">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="WINE-MERCHANT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The wine-merchant owns the cellar below Scrooge's house, where strange noises are heard</data>
      <data key="d6">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="HEARSE">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge imagines a hearse going up his staircase</data>
      <data key="d6">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GHOSTS">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge hears noises that he associates with ghosts dragging chains</data>
      <data key="d6">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="HAUNTED HOUSES">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge's house is described with elements typical of haunted houses</data>
      <data key="d6">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">6.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob Marley was Scrooge's business partner in life and now appears to him as a ghost
Jacob Marley sends supernatural messengers to Scrooge
Jacob Marley's memory haunts Scrooge, reminding him of his past
Jacob Marley predicted the arrival of the spirits to Scrooge
Jacob Marley is the ghost who warns Scrooge about the visits from the three spirits</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GHOST">
      <data key="d4">12.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is confronted by the ghost of Jacob Marley, which he initially disbelieves
The Ghost is guiding Scrooge through his past memories
The Ghost is guiding Scrooge through his past experiences
Scrooge interacts with the Ghost, reflecting on his past and experiencing a range of emotions
The Ghost is showing Scrooge scenes from his past to reflect on his life choices
The Ghost shows Scrooge visions of his life and influences his reflections
Scrooge speaks with the Ghost about Tiny Tim's future
The Ghost shows Scrooge visions of the future and rebukes him
The Ghost is guiding Scrooge through various scenes of Christmas celebrations
The Ghost is accompanying Scrooge and showing him various scenes
The Ghost is guiding Scrooge through various scenes</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c,bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf,c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="JACOB">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob appears to Scrooge to warn him about his fate and the visits of three spirits
Jacob was Scrooge's old partner</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Three Spirits will visit Scrooge to offer him a chance to change his fate</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="PHANTOMS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge sees phantoms wandering in the air, lamenting their inability to interfere in human matters</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="MARKET-TOWN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recognizes the market-town from his past</data>
      <data key="d6">3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="COUNTRY ROAD">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Ghost of Christmas Past stand on the country road</data>
      <data key="d6">3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHRISTMAS PAST">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Past shows Scrooge scenes from his past</data>
      <data key="d6">3763b08136628f77304cb4eb1136ea48</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="ALI BABA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls Ali Baba fondly from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="VALENTINE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls Valentine from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="ORSON">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls Orson from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="DAMASCUS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls a story involving a character at the gate of Damascus</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SULTAN'S GROOM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls the Sultan's Groom from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GENII">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls the Genii from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="PARROT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls the Parrot from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="ROBIN CRUSOE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls Robin Crusoe from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="FRIDAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge recalls Friday from his childhood imagination</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge visits the mansion with the Ghost</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="HIGH-ROAD">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Ghost leave the high-road to approach the mansion</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="LANE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Ghost travel down a well-remembered lane to reach the mansion</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">11.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit is guiding Scrooge through his past memories
The Spirit is showing Scrooge scenes from his past to reflect on his life choices
Scrooge interacts with the Spirit to learn lessons
Scrooge interacts with the Spirit, questioning him about his actions and intentions
The Spirit is guiding Scrooge through various scenes of Christmas celebrations
The Spirit is accompanying Scrooge and showing him various scenes
The Spirit shows Scrooge visions of the future and warns him about Ignorance and Want
The Spirit is guiding Scrooge through various scenes
Scrooge interacts with the Spirit, asking it to show him someone who feels emotion caused by the man's death
The Spirit is guiding Scrooge through various scenes
Scrooge interacts with the Spirit, pleading for a chance to change his ways</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c,b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd,f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="BOY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The boy represents Scrooge's younger self</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SCHOOLMASTER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The schoolmaster interacts with Scrooge and his sister during their childhood</data>
      <data key="d6">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="WAREHOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge was apprenticed at the warehouse where Fezziwig worked</data>
      <data key="d6">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="DICK">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge remembers his past with Dick, one of the apprentices</data>
      <data key="d6">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="FAIR YOUNG GIRL">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The fair young girl speaks to Scrooge about how his pursuit of wealth has displaced her</data>
      <data key="d6">bf29edcb41403e5af43aa101072f4fdf</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GIRL">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The girl was once in a relationship with Scrooge, which ended due to his pursuit of wealth
Scrooge asks the girl if her master is at home and she shows him upstairs</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="OFFICE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is seen by Belle's husband in his office</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="BEDROOM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge finds himself in his bedroom after his encounter with the Ghost</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SECOND OF THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The second spirit visits Scrooge after the first spirit</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CITY STREETS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Spirit stand in the city streets on Christmas morning</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">4.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge observes the events and interactions on Christmas Day
Scrooge is the subject of a toast on Christmas Day
Scrooge wakes up on Christmas Day after his transformative experience with the spirits
Scrooge is experiencing a transformation in his attitude and actions on Christmas Day</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588,1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">4.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge shows concern for Tiny Tim's future and asks the Ghost about it
Scrooge is concerned about Tiny Tim's health
Scrooge compares the size of the turkey to Tiny Tim
Scrooge becomes a second father to Tiny Tim and ensures his well-being</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,2b5ecb7fba1301d1f3d307e194a6c435,5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746,6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="FOUNDER OF THE FEAST">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is referred to as the Founder of the Feast by Bob Cratchit</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SCROOGE'S NIECE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge's niece is related to Scrooge and has strong opinions about his wealth and behavior</data>
      <data key="d6">bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="LONDON">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge lives in London, which is also where the animal in the guessing game lives</data>
      <data key="d6">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="TWELFTH-NIGHT PARTY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Spirit visited a children's Twelfth-Night party</data>
      <data key="d6">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHRISTMAS HOLIDAYS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Spirit traveled together during the Christmas holidays</data>
      <data key="d6">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="ALMSHOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Spirit visited an almshouse where they observed cheerfulness despite poverty</data>
      <data key="d6">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="HOSPITAL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Spirit visited a hospital where they observed cheerfulness despite illness</data>
      <data key="d6">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GAOL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Spirit visited a gaol where they observed cheerfulness despite imprisonment</data>
      <data key="d6">61a042016835080f3d334560b13b0e35</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="OLD JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Old Jacob Marley predicted the arrival of the spirits to Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="PHANTOM">
      <data key="d4">5.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Phantom, also known as the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come, shows Scrooge the future
The Phantom is guiding Scrooge through various scenes
Scrooge is accompanied by the Phantom
Scrooge glances towards the Phantom in terror
Scrooge is being guided by the Phantom through a fearful experience</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792,98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7,bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6,cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822,ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHANGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Phantom are in Change, a part of the City</data>
      <data key="d6">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="MERCHANTS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge observes the merchants in the City</data>
      <data key="d6">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="BUSINESS MEN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge listens to the business men discussing the death of an unknown person</data>
      <data key="d6">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="RED-FACED GENTLEMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge listens to the red-faced gentleman discussing the death of an unknown person</data>
      <data key="d6">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GREAT FAT MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge listens to the great fat man discussing the death of an unknown person</data>
      <data key="d6">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="OLD SCRATCH">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Old Scratch is mentioned in a conversation that Scrooge overhears</data>
      <data key="d6">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="TOWN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge visits an obscure part of the town</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SHOP">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge visits Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="INFAMOUS RESORT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge visits an infamous part of the town</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="UNHAPPY MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is horrified by the treatment of the unhappy man's belongings</data>
      <data key="d6">bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="ROOM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is in the room with the dead man and the Phantom</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="BED">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge observes the bed where the dead man lies</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="HOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge is in the dark, empty house where the dead man lies</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="HEARTHSTONE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge hears the sound of gnawing rats beneath the hearthstone</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="DOOR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge notices the cat tearing at the door in the room of death</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="THRESHOLD">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Spirit cross the threshold of Bob Cratchit's house</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CHURCHYARD">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge sees the grave with his name on it in the churchyard</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SPIRIT OF TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge mentions the spirit of Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="SCROOGE'S OFFICE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge sees his office with a different figure in the chair</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="IRON GATE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge and the Ghost of Christmas Yet to Come pass through the iron gate before entering the churchyard</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="GHOST OF CHRISTMAS FUTURE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost of Christmas Future shows Scrooge the potential future consequences of his actions</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="PAST">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge vows to honor and learn from the Past</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="PRESENT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge vows to honor and learn from the Present</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="FUTURE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge vows to honor and learn from the Future</data>
      <data key="d6">0f9b4e5a7cfc0c3c89a8898a45383588</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="CAMDEN TOWN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge plans to send the turkey to Camden Town</data>
      <data key="d6">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="PORTLY GENTLEMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge meets the portly gentleman and offers a generous donation</data>
      <data key="d6">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="POULTERER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge instructs the boy to buy the turkey from the poulterer</data>
      <data key="d6">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="LAD">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge asks the lad to buy the turkey and bring it to him</data>
      <data key="d6">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="JOE MILLER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge compares the joke of sending the turkey to Bob Cratchit to a joke by Joe Miller</data>
      <data key="d6">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="NIECE BY MARRIAGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge surprises his niece by marriage with his arrival at the dinner party</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE" target="MISTRESS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge asks the girl about the mistress, who is in the dining room</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARLEY" target="MARLEY'S FUNERAL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Marley's Funeral confirmed Marley's death</data>
      <data key="d6">10730234d6ccc7cee08f3cfc58d8a9a1</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARLEY" target="PROPHET'S ROD">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Marley's face is described as overshadowing other thoughts like the ancient Prophet's rod</data>
      <data key="d6">759315fa84c14e81f84fc71c73746184</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SCROOGE'S NEPHEW" target="SCROOGE'S NIECE">
      <data key="d4">3.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge's nephew and niece are married and share opinions about Scrooge
Scrooge's niece is part of the family and participates in the games, bringing joy to Scrooge's nephew</data>
      <data key="d6">4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6,bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="COUNTING-HOUSE" target="JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob Marley's spirit never roved beyond the counting-house in life</data>
      <data key="d6">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS EVE" target="JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob Marley died seven years ago on Christmas Eve</data>
      <data key="d6">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS EVE" target="MISS FEZZIWIGS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The three Miss Fezziwigs participate in the Christmas Eve celebration hosted by Fezziwig</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS EVE" target="WAREHOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Christmas Eve celebration takes place at the warehouse</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CITY" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The city is bustling with activities during Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CITY" target="CHANGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Change is a location within the city where merchants gather</data>
      <data key="d6">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="COURT" target="LABOURERS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Labourers are working at the corner of the court</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CLERK" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The clerk shares the nephew's positive views on Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="NEPHEW" target="CHRISTMAS">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The nephew values Christmas and believes it has done him good</data>
      <data key="d6">080d8e696ff38c653ca90fa086415e74</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="NEPHEW" target="NIECE BY MARRIAGE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Fred's wife is his niece by marriage</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="GHOST">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost shows Scrooge past Christmas events
The Ghost is spreading mirth and joy during Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c,ce95e4fc6ee410973c040fc628dce155</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="GREAT BRITAIN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The events and festive activities are taking place in Great Britain during Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="GROCER'S">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Grocer's is nearly closed but filled with festive items on Christmas morning</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="POULTERER'S">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Poulterer's is half open and selling goods on Christmas morning</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="FRUITERER'S">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Fruiterer's is radiant with fruits and other goods on Christmas morning</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="MASTER PETER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter is celebrating Christmas with his family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="MISS BELINDA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Miss Belinda is celebrating Christmas with her family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="MARTHA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha is celebrating Christmas with her family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim is celebrating Christmas with his family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Cratchit family is celebrating Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="DINNER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The dinner is part of the Cratchit family's Christmas celebration</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="MINERS">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The miners are celebrating Christmas in their hut</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="LIGHTHOUSE">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Two men in the lighthouse are celebrating Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="SHIP">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The crew on the ship is celebrating Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit is spreading mirth and joy during Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="OLD MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The old man is singing a Christmas song to his family</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="LAMPLIGHTER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The lamplighter laughs as the Spirit passes by, indicating the joy of Christmas</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="TWO MEN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The two men in the lighthouse celebrate Christmas by making a fire and singing</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="CREW">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The crew of the ship celebrate Christmas by humming tunes and sharing memories</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="SCROOGE'S NIECE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge's niece also enjoys Christmas and expresses strong opinions about it</data>
      <data key="d6">bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="TOPPER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Topper is involved in the Christmas gathering and expresses his opinions during the event</data>
      <data key="d6">bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS" target="SCROOGE'S NIECE'S SISTER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Scrooge's niece's sister participates in the Christmas festivities</data>
      <data key="d6">bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LORD MAYOR" target="MANSION HOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Lord Mayor resides in the Mansion House and oversees the city's Christmas celebrations</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LORD MAYOR" target="LITTLE TAILOR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Lord Mayor fined the little tailor for being drunk and bloodthirsty in the streets</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="ST. DUNSTAN" target="EVIL SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">St. Dunstan is known for his legendary battle with the Evil Spirit</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="POOR" target="GENTLEMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The gentleman is trying to raise funds to help the poor</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LABOURERS" target="MAIN STREET">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Labourers are repairing gas-pipes in the main street</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LABOURERS" target="GAS-PIPES">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Labourers are repairing the gas-pipes</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="RAGGED MEN AND BOYS" target="MAIN STREET">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Ragged men and boys are gathered around a fire in the main street</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LITTLE TAILOR" target="LEAN WIFE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The lean wife is the spouse of the little tailor</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LITTLE TAILOR" target="BABY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The baby is the child of the little tailor</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LEAN WIFE" target="BABY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The baby is the child of the lean wife</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHURCH" target="PEOPLE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">People flock to the church in their best clothes and with their gayest faces</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHURCH" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim went to the church with his father, Bob Cratchit.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MAIN STREET" target="WATER-PLUG">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The water-plug is located in the main street and has turned to ice</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MAIN STREET" target="SHOPS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Shops with bright windows are located in the main street</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SHOPS" target="POULTERERS' AND GROCERS' TRADES">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Poulterers' and grocers' trades are part of the shops in the main street</data>
      <data key="d6">0e2b719e4c97d0d8bfeb2a53f7638eb6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST" target="JACOB MARLEY">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob Marley appears as a ghost to Scrooge
Jacob Marley is the Ghost who visits Ebenezer Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416,e8d4072836ac08145edc2fa8c15ea2c2</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST" target="WARD">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ward would have been justified in indicting the Ghost for making noise</data>
      <data key="d6">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST" target="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit and the Ghost are the same entity showing Scrooge scenes from his past</data>
      <data key="d6">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GHOST" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Ghost shows Scrooge visions on Christmas Day</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="JACOB MARLEY" target="PHANTOM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob Marley is also referred to as the Phantom</data>
      <data key="d6">e3bef9514042131cf477476725497416</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="JACOB MARLEY" target="THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob Marley informs Scrooge about the visits of the Three Spirits</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PHANTOM" target="SPIRIT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Phantom and the Spirit are the same entity guiding Scrooge</data>
      <data key="d6">ebc403dd3df39bacc3443ef4afb7edfd</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PHANTOM" target="TOWN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Phantom accompanies Scrooge to an obscure part of the town</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PHANTOM" target="SHOP">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Phantom accompanies Scrooge to Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PHANTOM" target="INFAMOUS RESORT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Phantom accompanies Scrooge to an infamous part of the town</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="JACOB" target="THE THREE SPIRITS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Jacob informs Scrooge about the visits of the Three Spirits</data>
      <data key="d6">4ffd9df98742c035b3e15bb24c3edb12</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SPIRIT" target="CITY STREETS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit takes Scrooge to the city streets on Christmas morning</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SPIRIT" target="CHRISTMAS DAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit restores good humor among people on Christmas Day</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SPIRIT" target="BOB CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Spirit blesses Bob Cratchit's dwelling with the sprinklings of his torch</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SPIRIT" target="IGNORANCE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Ignorance is a boy shown to Scrooge by the Spirit</data>
      <data key="d6">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SPIRIT" target="WANT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Want is a girl shown to Scrooge by the Spirit</data>
      <data key="d6">98f3970b31dfa1d7391cdaa453d6ade7</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SULTAN'S GROOM" target="GENII">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Genii turned the Sultan's Groom upside down</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SULTAN'S GROOM" target="PRINCESS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Sultan's Groom was married to the Princess</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="ROBIN CRUSOE" target="FRIDAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Friday is Robin Crusoe's companion</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="STABLES" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The stables are part of the mansion's grounds</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="COACH-HOUSES" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The coach-houses are part of the mansion's grounds</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SHEDS" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The sheds are part of the mansion's grounds</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="HALL" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The hall is inside the mansion</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="ROOM" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The room is inside the mansion</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="ROOM" target="MATERN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The matron is in the room with her children</data>
      <data key="d6">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="ROOM" target="CHILDREN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The children are in the room with the matron</data>
      <data key="d6">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="ROOM" target="WINTER FIRE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The winter fire is a comforting element in the room where the matron and her children are gathered</data>
      <data key="d6">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="STOREHOUSE" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The storehouse is part of the mansion's grounds</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="YARD" target="MANSION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The yard is part of the mansion's grounds</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="YARD" target="POPPLAR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The poplar tree is in the yard</data>
      <data key="d6">206c2f9fd249659c7a897d323459cb6f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="WAREHOUSE" target="EBENEZER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Ebenezer works at the warehouse and participates in the Christmas Eve celebration</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="WAREHOUSE" target="MISS FEZZIWIGS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The three Miss Fezziwigs participate in the Christmas Eve celebration at the warehouse</data>
      <data key="d6">260fb94666cbdfb08286ce8d8162130d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GIRL" target="MATERN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The matron is the same girl from Scrooge's past, now grown and with children</data>
      <data key="d6">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MATERN" target="CHILDREN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The matron is the mother of the children in the scene</data>
      <data key="d6">d453d198afec5b284ff36024780b088c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHILDREN" target="FATHER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The father is greeted by his children who excitedly interact with the Christmas toys and presents he brings</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHILDREN" target="PARLOUR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The children and their emotions are described in the parlour</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHILDREN" target="MOTHER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The mother is anxiously waiting while her children play</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHILDREN" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim is one of the Cratchit children</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHILDREN" target="PETER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Peter is one of the Cratchit children</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MOTHER" target="FATHER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The father sits with his wife by the fireside</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MOTHER" target="FIRESIDE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The mother sits with her husband and daughter by the fireside</data>
      <data key="d6">c79e67fc6f74a9afbe79c158000cc71b</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MOTHER" target="WINDOW">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The mother looks out from the window anxiously</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MOTHER" target="CLOCK">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The mother glances at the clock while waiting</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PARLOUR" target="OLD JOE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Old Joe invites the characters into the parlour</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PARLOUR" target="LAUNDRESS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The laundress enters the parlour</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PARLOUR" target="UNDERTAKER'S MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The undertaker's man enters the parlour</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PARLOUR" target="CHARWOMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The charwoman enters the parlour</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PEOPLE" target="CITY STREETS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The people are shoveling snow and engaging in festive activities in the city streets</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PEOPLE" target="HOUSE-TOPS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The people are shoveling snow and engaging in jovial activities on the house-tops</data>
      <data key="d6">b029f1164f623c14a0cfaa73c246f50d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PEOPLE" target="CHAPEL">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">People flock to the chapel in their best clothes and with their gayest faces</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CHRISTMAS DAY" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Christmas Day is significant for Tiny Tim as it is a day of hope and inspiration for him, despite his condition.
Tiny Tim celebrates Christmas Day with his family</data>
      <data key="d6">1bdf253855a115bcf51faa63d7b07e82,b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="BAKER" target="DINNER-CARRIERS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The baker interacts with the dinner-carriers who bring their dinners to the baker's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="GROCER" target="CUSTOMERS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The grocer and his people serve the customers during the Christmas rush</data>
      <data key="d6">29793cee69d4eefd5fea8a5f2f27b521</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MASTER PETER CRATCHIT" target="TINY TIM">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter Cratchit and Tiny Tim are brothers, with Peter helping to fetch the goose and being part of the family celebration.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MASTER PETER CRATCHIT" target="CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter Cratchit lives in the Cratchit dwelling with his family.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="CRATCHIT'S DWELLING">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim lives in the Cratchit dwelling with his family.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="WASH-HOUSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim was taken to the wash-house by his siblings to hear the pudding singing in the copper.</data>
      <data key="d6">b4dec8fbe9f2a2c6a79d09c9484d15ae</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="MASTER PETER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim and Master Peter are siblings and part of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="MISS BELINDA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim and Miss Belinda are siblings and part of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="MARTHA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim and Martha are siblings and part of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim is a member of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="DINNER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim is participating in the family dinner</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="PETER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Peter is the sibling of Tiny Tim</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="SUNDAY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Tiny Tim's grave is visited by Bob Cratchit on Sunday</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TINY TIM" target="BOB">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob speaks fondly of Tiny Tim and remembers him</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MASTER PETER" target="MISS BELINDA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter and Miss Belinda are siblings and part of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MASTER PETER" target="MARTHA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter and Martha are siblings and part of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MASTER PETER" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter is a member of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MASTER PETER" target="DINNER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Master Peter is participating in the family dinner</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MISS BELINDA" target="MARTHA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Miss Belinda and Martha are siblings and part of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MISS BELINDA" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Miss Belinda is a member of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MISS BELINDA" target="DINNER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Miss Belinda is participating in the family dinner</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARTHA" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha is a member of the Cratchit family</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MARTHA" target="DINNER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Martha is participating in the family dinner</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="DINNER" target="CRATCHIT FAMILY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Cratchit family is having a dinner together</data>
      <data key="d6">5d70b47bf7167b7586f47fcc4355a746</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MINERS" target="BLEAK AND DESERT MOOR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The miners live on the bleak and desert moor</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="MINERS" target="HUT">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The miners and their families are celebrating Christmas in the hut</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LIGHTHOUSE" target="SEA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The lighthouse is built on a dismal reef of sunken rocks in the sea</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="SHIP" target="SEA">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The ship is far away from any shore, in the middle of the sea</data>
      <data key="d6">999c9887098d1a25dc3b42a8da7ddc8c</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TOPPER" target="SCROOGE'S NIECE'S SISTER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Topper has a romantic interest in Scrooge's niece's sister</data>
      <data key="d6">bc5fde5d1e00a3ecc1e548c8d24f1c1f</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TOPPER" target="PLUMP SISTER">
      <data key="d4">3.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Topper often pursues the plump sister during the game of blind man's-buff
Topper and the plump sister are both guests at Fred's dinner party</data>
      <data key="d6">04e5c071e4ee5496d5380662e1339f45,4cf4deeb7f61acb7b7db4ce0e57fb1e6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="OLD JOE" target="SHOP">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Old Joe owns and operates the shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="OLD JOE" target="LAUNDRESS">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The laundress interacts with Old Joe in his shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="OLD JOE" target="UNDERTAKER'S MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The undertaker's man interacts with Old Joe in his shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="OLD JOE" target="CHARWOMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The charwoman interacts with Old Joe in his shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LAUNDRESS" target="UNDERTAKER'S MAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The laundress and the undertaker's man meet in Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LAUNDRESS" target="CHARWOMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The charwoman and the laundress meet in Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="UNDERTAKER'S MAN" target="CHARWOMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The charwoman and the undertaker's man meet in Old Joe's shop</data>
      <data key="d6">1cb66ea16e5e4f2816f0e188d3acc792</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="TOWN" target="CAROLINE'S HUSBAND">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Caroline's husband brings news of the creditor's death in the town</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="UNHAPPY MAN" target="WOMAN">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The woman took items from the unhappy man's belongings</data>
      <data key="d6">bc606176c752984da6d202275ee8c7a6</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="CAROLINE'S HUSBAND" target="CREDITOR">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Caroline's husband brings the news of the creditor's death</data>
      <data key="d6">cd8a47ace09b9cee1e8b27b0689f2822</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PETER" target="BOOK">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Peter is reading a book</data>
      <data key="d6">f40e4b274b5e1a25afbff9ecb733e1f4</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PETER" target="BOB">
      <data key="d4">2.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Bob mentions that Peter might get a better situation</data>
      <data key="d6">19f8fd68a8dbc1bba7058e13ce3a2e3d</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="LAD" target="POULTERER">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The lad knows the poulterer and is asked to buy the turkey from him</data>
      <data key="d6">6c362d3f8d01c76d84443dcabf3f322a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG LITERARY ARCHIVE FOUNDATION" target="PROJECT GUTENBERG LICENSE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation enforces the Project Gutenberg License</data>
      <data key="d6">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG LITERARY ARCHIVE FOUNDATION" target="PROJECT GUTENBERG&#8482; TRADEMARK">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation owns the Project Gutenberg&#8482; trademark</data>
      <data key="d6">aa8d2310a206001404282ddb3fd645aa</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG LITERARY ARCHIVE FOUNDATION" target="FOUNDATION">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Foundation is another name for the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation</data>
      <data key="d6">0ddc17ea5e566006c000b4013f2181a5</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="PROJECT GUTENBERG LITERARY ARCHIVE FOUNDATION" target="SALT LAKE CITY">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">Salt Lake City is the location of the business office of the Project Gutenberg Literary Archive Foundation.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FOUNDATION" target="MISSISSIPPI">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Foundation is organized under the laws of Mississippi.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FOUNDATION" target="INTERNAL REVENUE SERVICE">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The Foundation was granted tax-exempt status by the Internal Revenue Service.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
    <edge source="FOUNDATION" target="UTAH">
      <data key="d4">1.0</data>
      <data key="d5">The business office of the Foundation is located in Utah, specifically in Salt Lake City.</data>
      <data key="d6">cd4234ed6caba8f15d09a2e3ee604b2a</data>
    </edge>
  </graph>
</graphml>